# **BARTOSZ MYLKA**

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER















#### **ABOUT**

I have been passionate about IT for many years. Lately, the field of coding particularly caught my interest. That's why recently I have decided to retrain myself at Coders Lab. In the near future I hope to combine my communication and language skills with my newly acquired coding skills.

#### TRAINING

#### **Coders Lab**

03/2017 - 04/2017

Bootcamp become Front-End Developer: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, ECMAScript 6, React, RWD, Sass, Git.

#### CONTACT



+48 504 505 230



bmylka@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/bartosz-mylka



github.com/BartekMy

### LANGUAGE

German - native speaker Polish - near native / fluent English - very good command

#### HOBBIES

#### **SKILLS**

IT Team player

Coding Strong written and verbal Reading communications skills

Sport / Fitness MS Office

Languages Driving licence Class B

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Becton Dickinson Polska Sp. z o.o.

01/2016 - 02/2017

Customer Service Complaints Handling Representative for the GSA markets (Germany, Switzerland and Austria)

# Irkutsk State Linguistic University, Irkutsk, Russia

09/2015 - 09/2015

Internship as a teacher of German language

### Stadtwerke Zittau GmbH, Zittau, Germany

09/2014 - 10/2014

Interpreter (Polish – German, German – Polish)

# Bernd Jorkisch GmbH & Co. KG, Daldorf, Germany

11/2006 - 06/2011

Dispatcher - Planing and organizing transports by road to South Germany and Europe (Forwarding and Logistics Services).

#### **EDUCATION**

# Hochschule Zittau / Görlitz - University of Applied Sciences

09/2011 - 11/2015

BA in translation English / Polish
Bachelor thesis: Software localization - General
theoretical introduction and the practical
implementation on the basis of chosen digital games